As new employees,
I'd like your opinion on our commercial.
I've paid to have it aired
during the Super Bowl.
- Wow.
- Not on the same channel, of course.
Interplanetary deliveries...
What a headache.
Evans, where is that package from earth?
Uh...
I'm not Evans!
He should have used Planet Express.
When those other companies
aren't brave or foolhardy enough to go,
trust Planet Express
for reliable, on-time delivery.
Here's your package,
Mr. Horrible Gelatinous Blob.
Good work, Evans.
You've got a future around here.
Thank you, sir.
Planet Express.
Our crew is replaceable,
your package isn't.
Are there really giant birds like that?
No, no, that was all
just special effects.
Now, let's have breakfast.
I hope everyone likes eggs.
I'm never going to get used
to the 31st century.
Caffeinated bacon?
Baconated grapefruit?
Admiral Crunch?
Well, if you don't like that
try some Archduke Chocula.
Ah, Hermes.
Crew, meet Hermes Conrad.
He manages my delivery business.
Pays the bills,
notifies next of kin, what have you.
Someone come and drop this package
through the slot last night.
Now, which one of you
is the captain?
Oh, my. I haven't picked
a new captain yet.
It's always so hard to choose.
Ooh. Ooh, ooh, ooh!
Mmm... You.
Okay, Captain,
this is just a standard legal release
protecting Planet Express from lawsuits
in the event of the unforeseen.
- "Death by airlock failure."
- Mm-hmm.
- "Death by brain parasite."
- Ya.
"Death by sonic diarrhea."
Oh, you don't want that.
Look, I don't know
about your previous captains,
but I intend to do
as little dying as possible.
Sign the paper.
And now, Fry,
before you go into space
you'll need to see our staff doctor.
I should warn you, though,
he's a little unusual.
He wears sandals.
Dr. Zoidberg, this is Fry,
the new delivery boy.
He needs a physical.
Excellent, excellent.
You'll be fine.
Now, open your mouth
and let's have a look at that brain.
No, no, no, not that mouth.
I only have one.
Really?
Uh... Is there a human doctor around?
Young lady, I'm an expert on humans.
Now pick a mouth, open it, and say...
Uh...
What? My mother was a saint!
Get out!
Dear Lord, Bender, you're filthy.
Yeah, like you don't
have crap in your neck.
Amy, why don't you give his body
a going-over with the cleaning pick?
Okay.
Does it hurt when I go like this?
Ow!
A little.
Well, the doctor says
I'm as healthy as a crab.
Can I go into space now?
As soon as we finish cleaning Bender.
Oh, and Fry...
This is our intern, Amy Wong.
She's an engineering student of mine.
I like having her around
because she has
the same blood type as me.
Hey, you're the unfrozen guy
from the 20th century, right?
Last time I checked.
Hang on. Amy Wong, of the Mars Wongs?
Look, we're not as rich as everybody says.
Uh-huh. What sorority do you belong to?
Kappa Kappa Wong.
Hey, rich girl!
Look over here.
It's me, Bender.
I'm being entertaining.
La-la-la, look at my head
It's okay to look at my head
I got a big ol' head
And hey! Ho!
All right, show's over. I'm tired.
Ah, to be young again...
And also a robot.
Oh! Now, as I recall,
you youngsters
have a package to deliver.
Finally. Come on, Bender.
Let's mosey.
Nice catch, idiot.
So, where are we going anyway?
Nowhere special, the moon.
The moo... The moon?
The moon moon?
Wow, I'm going to be a famous hero
just like Neil Armstrong
and those other brave guys
no one ever heard of.
Oh! I love stuff like the moon.
Can I come, Leela?
Well... I guess so.
Just be careful.
I'd like to hold off
any major screw-ups
until at least
my second day as captain.
Nothing will go wrong.
If something goes wrong
bring back the blood.
Can I do the countdown?
Huh? Oh, sure.
Knock yourself out.
Ten, nine...
Okay, we're here.
...eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one. Blastoff.
Hurry up.
I want to see the moon.
Relax, it's open till 9:00.
That's one small step for Fry...
And one giant line for admission.
Wow!
Um... Can I have cuts?
Hmm... Mmm...
No!
You're not going to believe this,
but they landed
an amusement park on the moon.
Guh! It's the happiest place
orbiting earth.
Let's go already.
Fry, we have a crate to deliver.
Let's just dump it in the sewer
and say we delivered it.
Too much work.
Let's burn it and say
we dumped it in the sewer.
Okay, if everyone's finished
being stupid...
I had more, but you go ahead.
We'll deliver that crate
like professionals
and then we'll go home.
But I've never been
to the moon before.
Oh, all right.
We'll deliver that crate
like professionals
And then we'll go
ride the bumper cars.
Amy, why don't you help Fry
hoist down the crate?
Then lock up when you're done.
Just be careful.
Aye, aye, Captain.
I mean, only one eye.
I mean, yes, sir... um, ma'am.
- Clear?
- Clear.
- Ready to hoist?
- Ready.
Ow!
My first space delivery.
Greetings, moon man.
We come in peace.
I am Fry, from the planet Earth.
Wise guy, huh?
If I wasn't so lazy
I'd punch you in the stomach.
But you are lazy, right?
Oh, don't get me started.
Hi! I'm Craterface.
Welcome to Luna Park.
I'll have to confiscate
your alcohol, sir.
Better mascots than you have tried.
At least I still have my self-respect.
Ugh, who buys this trash?
Idiots who need gifts for other idiots.
Hey, I got you guys
refrigerator magnets.
Get it off. Get it off!
Get it... Uh-oh.
How many roads
must a man walk down
Before you...
Keep those things off of me.
Magnets screw up my inhibition unit.
So you flip out and start acting
like some crazy folk singer?
Yes. I guess a robot
would have to be crazy
to want to be a folk singer.
We're whalers on the moon,
we carry a harpoon
But there ain't no whales,
so we tell tall tales
And sing our whaling tune
Bender! Hey, Bender! Over here!
Oh, geez, I went to
high school with that guy.
Monsanto presents...
The Goophy Gopher Revue.
Why does a moon rock
taste better than an earth rock?
Because it's a little "meteor."
This is weak.
Address all complaints
to the Monsanto corporation.
What's wrong, Fry?
I don't know.
This place is great and all
but it's just so artificial.
The gravity, the air, the gophers.
You might as well stay on earth.
That's what I came to see.
I want to go out there
and jump around like an astronaut.
Screw this phony stuff.
But the phony stuff is what's fun.
It's boring out there.
Yeah. You're the kind of guy
who visits Jerusalem
and doesn't want to see
the "Sexateria."
Maybe I should take Fry
on the Lunar Rover Ride.
You get to wear a space suit
and drive around on the surface
And the line's short
because it's educational.
I don't care how educational it is.
Let's do it!
Next year in Jerusalem!
Two adults, please.
Finally, get ready
for some serious moon action.
The story of lunar exploration
started with one man...
A man with a dream.
One of these days, Alice.
Bang! Zoom!
Straight to the moon!
Wow. I never realized
the first astronauts were so fat.
That's not an astronaut.
It's a TV comedian.
He was just using space travel
as a metaphor for beating his wife.
Wow! I could swear I was
really playing Virtual Skeeball.
- Hmm?
- Look, it's that crate
we were going to throw in the sewer.
The keys to the ship!
They must have fallen into the crate.
Leela's going to kill me.
Nah. She'll probably make me do it.
Mister, could you please
get those keys out for me?
What do I look like,
a guy who's not lazy?
No one knows where,
when or how man first landed on the moon.
- I do.
- But our fungineers think
It might have happened
something like this.
We're whalers on the moon
We carry a harpoon
But there ain't no whales
so we tell tall tales
And sing a whaling tune
That's not how it happened.
Oh, really? I don't see you
with a fungineering degree.
This is stupid.
I'm taking this thing
out to the real moon.
Fry, no. This is my first mission
and I'm not going to let us
get in any trouble.
Besides, the car's on a track.
Not for long.
We're whalers...
Oh! Ow!
I died doing what I loved.
Okay, you're on the surface.
Now, I'll give you ten minutes.
then you'll get bored, turn around
and apologize for being such a jerk.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
Yee-ha!
Yeah! Crank up the radio!
We're whalers on the...
Yee-ha!
Time's up.
Make a U-turn at the next crater.
No, not yet.
How about we go look
for the original moon landing site?
That's crazy.
It's been lost for centuries.
Well, I'm feeling lucky.
Ooh.
Uh... I'm ready to go back now.
We're going to die!
It's every man for himself!
Help me, Leela!
Whoo!
You did it.
We're safe.
No. Now we're going to die.
It's every man for himself!
Hey, look what I won
from a tourist's pocket.
Shut up. You're distracting me.
Come on, it's just like making love.
You know, left, down,
rotate 62 degrees
Engage rotor.
I know how to make love.
Here, let me do it.
Oh, lousy arm must be rigged.
That's her, officers.
That's the woman
who programmed me for evil.
Yeah, well, I'm going to go
build my own theme park
With blackjack and hookers.
In fact, forget the park.
I'm sorry, Leela.
I can't go on any further.
Just leave me to die
in that barn over there.
Oh, thank God.
Trespassers, eh?
No, sir. We're amusement park patrons.
Ooh, that's a wicked, sinful place.
Tilt-a-whirl's okay,
but the rest is mighty wicked.
Our car broke down
and we're out of oxygen.
Can we borrow some?
"Borry?" Looky here, city girl,
oxygen don't grow on trees.
You'll have to earn it doing chores
on my hydroponic farm.
You can go back to your precious
theme park at sunup.
I guess we could do chores
for a few hours.
Fry, night lasts two weeks on the moon.
Yep. Drops down to minus 173.
Fahrenheit or Celsius?
First one, then the other.
And them space suits ain't a-heated
so you ain't going nowhere till sunrise.
You can sleep in the barn.
Just don't be a-touchin'
my three beautiful
robot daughters, you hear?
Robot daughters?
This here's Lulabelle 7...
Yoo-hoo.
Daisy Mae 128-K...
And the Crushinator.
Yoo-hoo.
Whoa!
I told you to turn around
and go back to the park.
But, oh, no.
The park was too phony.
We had to see the real moon.
And it was great.
We got to see craters and rocks
and that one incredible rock
that looked like a crater
And... And these fellas.
Fry, face it, the moon is a dump.
It's a boring dried-up wasteland.
And the only reason
anybody ever comes here
is for the tacky
little amusement park.
Can't you just accept that?
I guess I can't.
I'll learn you to sleep
with my robot daughters.
He'll never find me in here.
Bender?
Ugh. Bender, you didn't touch
the Crushinator, did you?
Of course not. A lady that fine
you got to romance first.
Oh, no, you don't.
Come here, Crushinator.
Yes, Pa.
- It's too low!
- Hang on.
Hang on. Jump!
Hold on to your helmet.
Whoa!
- Yes!
- Oh, boy.
Goldurn it, Crushinator, jump!
No, Pa. I love him.
Oh!
Hey, cool. Dark side of the moon.
Nightfall's coming.
Hurry, before we freeze.
What do you mean we, mammal?
Oh, dear.
I really ought to do something.
But I'm already in my pajamas.
We can't outrun it forever.
Over there. Look!
It's the moon landing site.
We found it.
Quick, get in.
It's that flag from MTV.
And Neil Armstrong's footprint.
Hey, my foot's bigger.
Leela, isn't this the greatest
thing you've ever seen?
Fry, look around.
It's just a crummy plastic flag
and a dead man's tracks in the dust.
Now, get in here before you freeze.
Oh, no room for Bender, huh?
Fine, I'll go build my own lunar lander
With blackjack and hookers.
In fact, forget the lunar lander
and the blackjack.
Ah, screw the whole thing.
Well, if the oxygen holds out,
we might live long enough
to starve to death.
Look, Leela, I'm sorry.
I never should have dragged you out here.
That's right. You shouldn't have.
I still don't get
what the big attraction is.
I never told anybody this
but a thousand years ago,
I used to look up at the moon
and dream about being an astronaut.
I just didn't have the grades
or the physical endurance.
Plus, I threw up a lot
and nobody likes
spending a week with me.
A week would be a little much.
The moon was like this awesome,
romantic, mysterious thing
hanging up there in the sky
where you could never reach it
no matter how much you wanted to.
But you're right.
Once you're actually here,
it's just a big dull rock.
I guess I just wanted you
to see it through my eyes
The way I used to.
Fry, look.
It really is beautiful.
I don't know why
I never noticed before.
Had to come back
for the Crushinator, eh, robot?
Well, I got you this time.
It's Amy. We're saved.
Amy?
Where'd she learn to operate
the controls like that?
Not the magnet.
No! No! No!
Uh-oh.
She'll be coming around
the mountain when she comes
I'll kill you, Amy!
She'll be coming around the mountain
She'll be coming around
the mountain, she'll be...
Ah, dang it.
She'll be riding six
white horses when she comes
whitehorses when she comes
Hey, I'm pretty good.
She'll be riding
six white horses
So, Fry, was the real moon
anything like the moon
you used to dream about?
Uh... Close enough.
Well, I'll shoot her
with my ray-gun when she comes
Yes, I'll shoot her
Yes, I'll shoot her with my ray-gun
Oh, I'llshoot her with my ray-gun
Yes, I'll shoot her withmy ray-gun
when she comes, when she comes
I'll be blasting
all the humans in the world
I'll be blasting all the humans
I'll be blasting
all the humans in the world
In the world
One more time!